<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hack computer systems like black hat on Hacksec</title>
    <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hack computer systems like black hat on Hacksec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.hacksec.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shodan</title>
      <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/shodan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/shodan/</guid>
      <description>Shodan Use In Bug Bounty What is shodan Shodan is a search engine that lets users search for various types of servers (webcams, routers, servers, etc.) connected to the internet using a variety of filters. Some have also described it as a search engine of service banners, which are metadata that the server sends back to the client. This can be information about the server software, what options the service supports, a welcome message or anything else that the client can find out before interacting with the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nmap</title>
      <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/nmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/nmap/</guid>
      <description>What is NMAP Nmap is a free and open-source network scanner created by Gordon Lyon. Nmap is used to discover hosts and services on a computer network by sending packets and analyzing the responses. Nmap provides a number of features for probing computer networks, including host discovery and service and operating system detection.
What Does Nmap Do? Nmap (Network Mapper) is an open source and free security scanner used for network discovery and security auditing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recon</title>
      <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/getting_started_with_recon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/getting_started_with_recon/</guid>
      <description>Reconnaissance So here is our another article regarding recon&amp;hellip;
Reconnaissance attacks are general knowledge gathering attacks
Google dork A Google query, sometimes just referred to as a dork, is a search string that uses advanced search operators to find information that is not readily available on a website
Some google dork example   site:&amp;quot;.uk&amp;quot; intitle:&amp;ldquo;admin login&amp;rdquo; [Pages Containing Login Portals]
  &amp;ldquo;Not for Public Release&amp;rdquo; + &amp;ldquo;Confidential&amp;rdquo; ext:pdf | ext:doc | ext:xlsx [Files Containing Juicy Info]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hacksec-cli</title>
      <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/hacksec_cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/hacksec_cli/</guid>
      <description>What is hacksec-cli hacksec-CLI is a command-line tool written in python3 which allow you to access all hacksec services directly from your command-line.
Requirement  python3 git  How to install in linux command : curl -s -L https://raw.githubusercontent.com/hacksec-in/hacksec-cli/main/install.sh | bash How to install in windows  git clone https://github.com/hacksec-in/hacksec-cli cd hacksec-cli python3 install.py  Why hacksec-cli This is the beta version of hacksec-cli. Soon we will add more features like one-click lab deployment in your local machines and we will add our tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find me writeup</title>
      <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/_findme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hacksec.in/posts/_findme/</guid>
      <description>Web-Lab information Find ME          Point: 30+   Level: MEDIUM   Target: http://machine4.hacksec.in   First ownby: H3X1337   Created by: SCRIPT1337X    let&amp;rsquo;s start First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s see what we have to work on by opening the URL. Reconnaissance Ok so now we start our reconnaissance, first we try to find all the hidden folders of the website using Dirb with default wordlist common.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blog.hacksec.in/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.hacksec.in/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to hacksec We develop tools and software for making pentesting easy and securing your network. Founded in 2021 by script1337, We hope you enjoy our products as much as we enjoy offering them to you. If you have any questions or comments, please don’t hesitate to contact us.
Why choose hacksec?  Our services are free for individuals. Hacksec is more than just a pentesting lab Our real-life inspired labs will help you to get better at finding bugs and write your exploits,scripts and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
